Finding Aid for Michigan United Conservation Clubs records, 1937-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- People File
  - 9x6 Envelopes
    - Clarke, Hansen (Box 22)
    - Clarkson, James (Box 22)
    - Cleary, James F. (Box 22)
    - Clodfelter, Mark (Box 22)
    - Clute, Rod (Box 22)
    - Cogswell, Thomas (Box 22)
    - Compeau, Robert J. (Box 22)
    - Conklin, David (Box 22)
    - Connors, Jim (Box 22)
    - Conroy, Joseph (Box 22)
    - Conway, Dennis (Box 22)
    - Conyers, John Jr. (Box 22)
    - Cool, K. L. (Box 22)
    - Cooley, Mark (Box 22)
    - Cooper, Daniel S. (Box 22)
    - Coppens, Betty Lou (Box 22)
    - Corbett, Glenn (Box 22)
    - Corbin, Gary G. (Box 22)
    - Cory, Larry (Box 22)
    - Cotter, David G. (Box 22)
    - Courtemanche, Verna (Box 22)
    - Crabtree, Marietta (Box 22)
    - Cracknell, Ken (Box 22)
    - Cramton, Louis (Box 22)
    - Crim, Bobby (Box 22)
    - Criqui, Francis B. (Box 22)
    - Crissman, Penny (Box 22)
    - Cropsey, Alan L. (Box 22)
    - Cropsey, Harmon (Box 22)
    - Crosby, Bing (Box 22)
    - Crouse, Carl (Box 22)
    - Crowe, James A. O. (Box 22)
    - Cruce, Doug (Box 22)
    - Cruickshank, Arthur (Box 22)
    - Cullers, George (Box 22)
    - Curry, Dorias J. (Box 22)
    - Curtis, Candace A. (Box 22)
    - Cutler, M. Rupert (Box 22)
    - Dabb, James (Box 22)
    - Dahl, George (Box 22)
    - Dalman, Jessie (Box 22)
    - Daniel, Michael G. (Box 22)
    - Dansereau, Carol (Box 22)
    - Darling, Jay N. (Ding) (Box 22)
    - Daust, Warren E. (Box 22)
      (President, Bombardier Corp.)
    - Davenport, Earl (Box 22)
    - Davenport, La Verne A. (Box 22)
    - Davey, Joseph F. (Box 22)
    - Davis, Fred (Box 22)
    - Davis, Robert (Box 22)
    - Daw, T.E. (Ted) (Box 22)
    - Dean, Walter and Edna (Box 22)
    - DeBeaussaert, Ken (Box 22)
    - DeFebaugh, James E. (Box 22)
    - DeGeorge, Emil (Box 22)
    - DeGrow, Alvin (Box 22)
    - DeGrow, Dan L. (Box 22)
    - DeHart, Eileen (Box 22)
    - Delaney, James (Box 22)
    - DeLange, Walter J. (Box 22)
    - DeLisle, Dan (Box 22)
    - Delor, Walt (Box 22)
    - DeMars, Robert A. (Box 22)
    - De Maso, Harry A. (Box 22)
    - Denault, Charles H. Sr. (Box 22)
    - De Sana, James (Box 22)
    - De Stigter, Melvin (Box 22)
    - DeVillez, Robert (Box 22)
    - DeVuyst, Larry (Box 22)
    - Dewey, Gary (Box 22)
    - Dibean, Jack (Box 22)
    - Dillingham, Frederick (Box 22)
    - DiNello, Gilbert J. (Box 22)
    - Dingell, Christopher D. (Box 22)
    - Dishno, Dorothy (Box 22)
    - Dittmar, Arthur (Box 22)
    - Dively, Michael (Box 22)
    - Dobb, Barbara J. (Box 22)
    - Dobronski, Agnes (Box 22)
    - Docherty, James A. (Box 22)
    - Dodak, Lewis N. (Box 22)
    - Dohms, Jean (Box 22)
    - Dolan, Jan (Box 22)
    - Donahue, J. William (Box 22)
    - Douglas, David C. (Box 22)
    - Douglas, Nancy A. (Box 22)
    - Douglass, Donald W. (Box 22)
    - Doyle, Thomas R. (Box 22)
    - Dresch, Stephen P. (Box 22)
    - Dressel, James K. (Box 22)
    - Dubbs, James M. (Box 22)
    - DuCharme, Mark (Box 22)
    - Dudderar, Glenn (Box 22)
    - Dunaskiss, Mat (Box 22)
    - Dunham, Loren (JD) (Box 22)
    - Durling, Kurt Frederick (Box 22)
    - Dutko, Dennis M. (Box 22)
    - Dysart, Ben C. III (Box 22)
    - Easterbrook, Neal (Box 22)
    - Eddy, Gerald E. (Box 22)
    - Eder, Tim (Box 22)
    - Edwards, L. Thornton, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Ehlers, Vernon J. (Box 22)
    - Eichinger, John B. (Box 22)
    - Eisele, Paul (Box 22)
    - Eisele, Sally (Box 22)
    - Elden, Richard (Box 22)
    - Elliott, Arthur G. (Box 22)
    - Elliott, Daisy (Box 22)
    - Ellison, Eugene J. (Box 22)
    - Ells, Gar (Box 22)
    - Elmer, Art (Box 22)
    - Emerson, Robert (Box 22)
    - Emmons, Joann G. (Box 22)
    - Ehde, Dennis D. (Box 22)
    - Engler, Colleen (Box 22)
    - Engler, John M. (Box 22)
    - Erickson, Ed III (Box 22)
    - Erk, Lisa (Box 22)
    - Espinoza, James U. (Box 22)
    - Eustis, O.B. (Box 22)
    - Evans, David (Box 22)
    - Everett, David (Box 22)
    - Farhat, Debbie (Box 22)
    - Faught, Carolyn (Box 22)
    - Faust, William (Box 22)
    - Favero, Carol C. (Box 22)
    - Fears, J. Wayne (Box 22)
    - Feather, Noel (Box 22)
    - Fessler, Richard D. (Box 22)
    - Field, William (Box 22)
    - Fijalkowski, Dennis (Box 22)
    - Fink, David H. (Box 22)
    - Fiorucci, John (Box 22)
    - Fitzgerald, Frank M. (Box 22)
    - Fitzgerald, William B. (Box 22)
    - Fitzpatrick, Richard (Box 22)
    - Fluharty, Marlene J. (Box 22)
    - Fons, Valerie (Box 22)
    - Foote, James (Box 22)
    - Forbes, Joseph (Box 22)
    - Fox, Noel P. (Box 22)
    - Frailey, Kevin W. (Box 22)
    - Frankland, Kenneth P. (Box 22)
    - Fraser, Rev. William H. (Box 22)
    - Fredricks, Ed (Box 22)
    - Freels, Jerome L. (Box 22)
    - Freeman, Don (Box 22)
    - Freeman, John F. (Box 22)
    - Freeman, Stewart H. (Box 22)
    - Frimodig, David M. (Mac) (Box 22)
    - Fuller, Norman Stephen (Box 22)
    - Furtaw, Bill (Box 22)
    - Furton, George C. (Box 22)
    - Gagliardi, Pat (Box 22)
    - Gallagher, Janet E. (Box 22)
    - Galloway, David N. (Box 22)
    - Gapen, Dan (Box 22)
    - Garbutt, Barbara (Box 22)
    - Gardiner, Robert H., Jr. (Box 22)
    - Gardner, William (Box 22)
    - Gast, Harry Jr. (Box 22)
    - Gazlay, A. Gene (Box 22)
    - Geake, R. Robert (Box 22)
    - Geerlings, Edgar A. (Box 22)
    - Geerlings, Glenn (Box 22)
    - Geiger, Terry (Box 22)
    - Geilhart, Jim (Box 22)
    - Geoffrion, Bernard (Boom-Boom) (Box 22)
    - Geralds, Monte R. (Box 22)
    - Gernaat, John (Box 22)
    - Giese, Ed (Box 22)
    - Gilmer, Donald H. (Box 22)
    - Gingrass, Jack (Box 22)
    - Giordano, Peter (Box 22)
    - Gire, Sharon L. (Box 22)
    - Gnatkowski, Mike (Box 22)
    - Gnodtke, Carl F. (Box 22)
    - Goemaere, Warren N. (Box 22)
    - Gooch, Ralph (Box 22)
    - Goodman, George D. (Box 22)
    - Goodman, Gerald (Box 22)
    - Gordon, Guy (Box 22)
    - Goschka, Michael (Box 22)
    - Gougeon, Joel (Box 22)
    - Granger, Dale W. (Box 22)
    - Granholm, Jennifer (Box 22)
    - Gray, John (Box 22)
    - Green, Leonard A. (Box 22)
    - Green, Loren (Box 22)
    - Goodheart, James R. (Box 22)
    - Green, Mike (Box 22)
    - Greene, Howard C. (Bing) (Box 22)
    - Greenwalt, Lynn A. (Box 22)
    - Greenwood, Fred J., Jr. (Box 22)
    - Gregory, William (Box 22)
    - Greij, Eldon (Box 22)
    - Gresham, Grits (Box 22)
    - Griffin, Michael J. (Box 22)
    - Griffith, George (Box 22)
    - Griffith, Opal (Box 22)
    - Grimes, Robert (Box 22)
    - Grinnell, Alden (Ozzie) (Box 22)
    - Grischke, Todd A. (Box 22)
    - Groves, Ed (Box 22)
    - Gruninger, Karl M. (Box 22)
    - Gruse, Gregory G. (Box 22)
    - Guastello, Thomas (Box 22)
    - Gubow, David (Box 22)
    - Guenther, Charles J. (Box 22)
    - Guenther, Gary E. (Box 22)
    - Gullion, Gordon (Box 22)
    - Gustafson, Dan (Box 22)
    - Guyer, Gordon E. (Box 22)
    - Gwizdz, Bob (Box 22)
    - Gwynn, Rob (Box 22)
    - Hackett, Harold P. (Box 22)
    - Hadden, James (Box 22)
    - Hagan, Edward J., Jr. (Box 22)
    - Haines, Gerald (Box 22)
    - Hair, Jay D. (Box 22)
    - Hales, David F. (Box 22)
    - Hammerstrom, Beverly (Box 22)
    - Hammill, James (Box 22)
    - Hammon, Jack R. (Box 22)
    - Hand, Larry (Box 22)
    - Hall, Doug (Box 22)
    - Hanley, Michael (Box 22)
    - Harder, Clark (Box 22)
    - Harding, Russell (Box 22)
    - Harger, Elsworth (Box 22)
    - Harmes, Roland Jr. (Box 22)
    - Harrington, Patrick L. (Box 22)
    - Harris, Charles (Box 22)
    - Harris, John D. (Box 22)
    - Harrison, Charlie J. Jr. (Box 22)
    - Hart, George Z. (Box 22)
    - Hart, Jerome T. (Box 22)
    - Hart, Kay M. (Box 22)
    - Harvey, Jack (Box 22)
    - Hastings, Harold L. (Box 22)
    - Hayden, Larry (Box 22)
    - Hayes, Michael D. (Box 22)
    - Hays, Jon (Box 22)
    - Hays, Norma (Box 22)
    - Haywood, David (Box 22)
    - Heary, Nicholas G. (Box 22)
    - Heath, John (Box 22)
    - Heller, Clifton W. (Box 22)
    - Hellman, Rep. Russell (Box 22)
    - Hendriksma, Adrian (Box 22)
    - Hendrix, Eunice (Box 22)
    - Hendricksen, Michael C. (Box 22)
    - Henry, Susan E. (Box 22)
    - Herbst, David (Box 22)
    - Hertel, Curtis (Box 22)
    - Hertel, John C. (Box 22)
    - Hertling, Heiner (Box 22)
    - Hickner, Tom (Box 22)
    - Hill, A. Alan (Box 22)
    - Hill, James P. (Box 22)
    - Hill, Ransom (Box 22)
    - Hill, Sandra J. (Box 22)
    - Hillegonds, Paul (Box 22)
    - Hitchcock, Claudia (Box 22)
    - Hoefer, Jacob (Box 22)
    - Hokeman, Alvin J. (Box 22)
    - Hoffman, Philip (Box 22)
    - Hoffmaster, Percy James (Box 22)
    - Holcomb, Thomas M. (Box 22)
    - Holli, David (Box 22)
    - Hollister, David C. (Box 22)
    - Holly, I.B. (Box 22)
    - Holmes, David S. (Box 22)
    - Holmes, Kirby (Box 22)
    - Holmes, Robert (Box 22)
    - Honigman, David (Box 22)
    - Hood, Morris, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Hood, Raymond W., Jr. (Box 22)
    - Hoover, Wendell (Box 22)
    - Hopkins, Daniel W. (Box 22)
    - Horton, Jack (Box 22)
    - Horton, Jim (Box 22)
    - Hosford, Karl R. (Box 22)
    - Houghton, Douglass (Box 22)
    - Houk, Peter D. (Box 22)
    - Howard, Marc (Box 22)
    - Howard, William W. (Box 22)
    - Hoyt, Don Sr. (Box 22)
    - Huff, Terry (Box 22)
    - Huffman, Bill S. (Box 22)
    - Huggler, Thomas (Box 22)
    - Hull, Howard (Box 22)
    - Hulsey, George (Box 22)
    - Humphries, Rebecca (Box 22)
    - Hundzinski, Susan (Box 22)
    - Hunter, Teola P. (Box 22)
    - Inglis, Beatrice (Box 22)
    - Inman, Donald L. (Box 22)
    - Irwin, Mitch (Box 22)
    - Jacobetti, Dominic J. (Box 22)
    - Jager, Lee (Box 22)
    - Jameson, Richard L. (Box 22)
    - Karasek, Tim (Box 22)
    - Karmann, Norbert M. (Box 22)
    - Kaza, Greg (Box 22)
    - Keeler, Roy (Box 22)
    - Kehres, Raymond C. (Box 22)
    - Keith, William R. (Box 22)
    - Kelly, John F. (Box 22)
    - Kelly, Larry (Box 22)
    - Kelly, Sherman (Box 22)
    - Kelly, Thomas H. (Box 22)
    - Kelsey, John T. (Box 22)
    - Kemppainen, Gregory S. (Box 22)
    - Kendy, William (Box 22)
    - Kennaugh, John H. (Box 22)
    - Kennedy, Bela A. (Box 22)
    - Kerwin, James (Box 22)
    - Kildee, Dale E. (Box 22)
      (also see 8x10 file)
    - Kilpatrick, Carolyn C. (Box 22)
    - Kimball, Thomas L. (Box 22)
    - Kingren, Robert (Box 22)
    - Kirk-Hall, Peggy (Box 22)
    - Kirsey, Jack E. (Box 22)
    - Kitchel, Dr. John H. (Box 22)
    - Kling, Sherrill A. (Box 22)
    - Knapp, Dennis (Box 22)
    - Knickerbocker, Dennis C. (Box 22)
    - Knight, Marvin L. (Box 22)
    - Knock, Chuck (Box 22)
    - Koch, Mindy (Box 22)
    - Koivisto, Don (Box 22)
    - Kok, Peter (Box 22)
    - Kosteva, James A. (Box 22)
    - Kowalkowski, Bob (Box 22)
    - Kowelski, Chester (Box 22)
    - Krause, Victor C. (Box 22)
    - Kreger, William E. (Box 22)
    - Krokker, Richard (Box 22)
    - Krug, Alan (Box 22)
    - Kruger, Jon (Box 22)
    - Kruger, Verlen (Box 22)
    - Krumrey, Dietmar (Box 22)
    - Kukuk, Alvin (Box 22)
    - Kurta, Allen (Box 22)
    - Kurzmann, Andrew (Box 22)
    - Laich, Robert (Box 22)
    - Laidlaw, David O. (Box 22)
    - Laidler, Dennis (Box 22)
    - Laird, Thomas (Box 22)
    - Laitala, E.M. (Box 22)
    - LaLonde, Leo R. (Box 22)
    - Lambright, Wayne (Box 22)
    - Langley, Don (Box 22)
    - Lareau, Joseph (Box 22)
    - Larsen, Melvin L. (Box 22)
    - Laser, Dr. Kenneth D. (Box 22)
    - Laurie, Jack (Box 22)
    - Law, Gerald H. (Box 22)
    - Law, Robert C. (Box 22)
    - Lawrence, Rod (Box 22)
    - Lay, Cleamon (Cleon) (Box 22)
    - Laycock, William (Box 22)
    - Leach, Paul (Box 22)
    - LeBlanc, Lee (Box 22)
    - Legel, Jack E. (Box 22)
    - Lehman, F.R. (Pete) (Box 22)
    - Leland, Burton (Box 22)
    - Lennox, Thomas M. (Box 22)
    - Leopold, Aldo (Box 22)
    - Lester, Harry E. (Box 22)
    - LeTarte, Clyde (Box 22)
    - LeVasseur, David (Buck) (Box 22)
    - Leveridge, Walter J. (Box 22)
    - Lincoln, Everitt F. (Box 22)
    - Little, Gene (Box 22)
    - Little, Timothy (Box 22)
    - Littrell, Teri (Box 22)
    - Llewellyn, John T. (Box 22)
    - London, Terry (Box 22)
    - Long, Cliff (Box 22)
    - Loper, Barry C. (Box 22)
    - Lousma, Jack (Box 22)
    - Lowe, Allen L. (Box 22)
    - Lucas, William (Box 22)
    - Ludlam, Michael J. (Box 22)
    - Luhrs, Neil M. (Box 22)
    - Lujan, Manuel, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Lyman, Greg (Box 22)
    - Lynn, Loretta (Box 22)
    - MacEachern, Diane (Box 22)
    - MacGregor, John M. (Box 22)
    - Mack, Sen. Joseph (Box 22)
    - MacMullan, Ralph A. (Box 22)
    - Mainville, Frank (Box 22)
    - Malette, Peter J. (Box 22)
    - Malloch, William (Box 22)
    - Malski, Cindy (1985) (Box 22)
    - Marcus, Stan (Box 22)
    - Marshall, Frank (Box 22)
    - Martin, Al (Box 22)
    - Martin, Bob (Box 22)
      (1978 & 1979 MUCC State Shoot Skeet Champion)
    - Martin, Oliver B. (Box 22)
    - Martin, Thomas (Box 22)
    - Martin, William (Box 22)
    - Martinez, Lynne (Box 22)
    - Mastin, Philip O. (Box 22)
    - Mataczynski, David A. (Box 22)
    - Mathieu, Thomas C. (Box 22)
    - Matteson, Bruce (Box 22)
    - Mattson, Ellwood (Box 22)
    - Maynard, John M. (Box 22)
    - McBeath, Donald (Sandy) (Box 22)
    - McBryde, James (Box 22)
    - McCall, Thomas (Tom) (Box 22)
    - McCartney, Lori (Box 22)
    - McClelland, Nina (Box 22)
    - McClure, Harold M. Jr. (Box 22)
    - McCollough, Lucille H. (Box 22)
    - McCollough, Patrick H. (Box 22)
    - McCormack, C.S. and MaryAnn (Box 22)
    - McCoy, Roger (Box 22)
    - McGee, Robert D. (Box 22)
    - McLaughlin, Robert C. (Box 22)
    - McManus, George A., Jr. (Box 22)
    - McManus, Michelle A. (Box 22)
    - McManus, Patrick F. (Box 22)
    - McNamee, Ruth (Box 22)
    - McNary, James (Box 22)
    - McNeely, Matthew (Box 22)
    - McNutt, James (Box 22)
    - McPeek, Max R. (Box 22)
    - McPharlin, T. Edward (Box 22)
    - Meadows, C. Edward, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Mehan, G. Tracy III (Box 22)
    - Mehl, Janet D. (Box 22)
    - Meredith, Aldred (Box 22)
    - Meyer, Larry (Box 22)
    - Michigan Duck Hunters Association (Box 22)
    - Micka, Richard G. (Box 22)
    - Middaugh, James Mick (Box 22)
    - Middleton, Thomas (Box 22)
    - Migisiwa (Box 22)
    - Mikkelson, Joel (Box 22)
    - Mikula, Edward J. (Box 22)
    - Miller, Arthur, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Miller, Judith (Box 22)
    - Miller, Robert P. (Box 22)
    - Miller, Roberta (Box 22)
    - Miller, Volmar (Box 22)
    - Milliken, Helen (Box 22)
    - Milstein, Samuel A. (Box 22)
    - Mims, Walter L. (Box 22)
    - Misseldine, Carol (Box 22)
    - Mitchell, Robert (Box 22)
    - Mittan, Ray C. (Box 22)
    - Mize, Verna (Box 22)
    - Mohrhardt, David (Box 22)
    - Mol, Michael (Box 22)
    - Moll, Marge (Box 22)
    - Monroe, Michael Glenn (Box 23)
    - Monsma, Stephen V. (Box 23)
    - Montgomery, George (Box 23)
    - Moore, Michael D. (Box 23)
    - Moore, Michael J. (Box 23)
    - Moore, Richard X. (Box 23)
    - Morgan, Lewis Henry (Box 23)
    - Mottl, Henry (Box 23)
    - Mowat, John S. Jr. (Box 23)
    - Mrozinski, Leo (Box 23)
    - Mueller, Charles L. (Box 23)
    - Mullendore, William J. (Box 23)
    - Mullhaupt, Catherine (Box 23)
    - Munsell, Susan Grimes (Box 23)
    - Munson, Earl (Box 23)
      (1979 and 1980 MUCC State Shoot Trap Champion)
    - Murphy, Charles (Box 23)
    - Murphy, Raymond M. (Box 23)
    - Murray, James (Box 23)
    - Muxlow, Keith (Box 23)
    - Nash, Ernest (Box 23)
    - Nelson, Charles (Box 23)
    - Nichols, Rudy J. (Box 23)
    - Nicholson, Robert (Box 23)
    - Niederstadt, Roland G. (Box 23)
    - Nielsen, Mogens (Box 23)
    - North, Walter H. (Box 23)
    - Norton, Mike (Box 23)
    - Nowak, Mike (Box 23)
    - Nugent, Ted (Box 23)
    - Nye, Michael E. (Box 23)
    - O'Brien, Michael J. (Box 23)
    - O'Brien, Roy (Box 23)
    - O'Bryan, Barry (Box 23)
    - O'Connor, Margaret (Box 23)
    - Ogonowski, Casmer P. (Box 23)
    - Oil Well Fire (Box 23)
      (State-Diefenbach 1-3, June 1976)
    - Olsen, Eric R. P. (Box 23)
    - Olshove, Dennis (Box 23)
    - Olson, David D. (Box 23)
    - O'Neill, James E. Jr. (Box 23)
    - Opre, Tom (Box 23)
    - Osborn, Chase S. (Box 23)
    - Ostling, Ralph (Box 23)
    - Ott, Paul (Box 23)
    - Ottarson, James M. (Box 23)
    - Otterbacher, John R. (Box 23)
    - Ouwinga, Sidney (Box 23)
    - Owen, Gary M. (Box 23)
    - Owen, Lynn F. (Box 23)
    - Oxender, Glenn (Box 23)
    - Padden, Jeffrey D. (Box 23)
    - Paden, Mary (Box 23)
    - Pagen, Joseph (Box 23)
    - Palamara, Joseph (Box 23)
    - Paluda, Michael (Box 23)
    - Parfet, William U. (Box 23)
    - Opolka, Frank (Box 23)
    - Oppenlander, Paul (Box 23)
    - Parks, Mary Lou (Box 23)
    - Parrott, Mary Ellen (Box 23)
    - Partica, Earl (Box 23)
    - Pas, Richard (Box 23)
    - Patten, Gregory W. (Box 23)
    - Peacock, James (Box 23)
    - Pearce, Hale (Box 23)
    - Pemberton, Susan (Box 23)
    - Pengelly, Dr. W. Leslie (Box 23)
    - Pepperl, Joni (Box 23)
    - Perakis, Robert A. (Box 23)
    - Perricone, Charles (Box 23)
    - Perrish, Bob (Box 23)
    - Peters, Gary C. (Box 23)
    - Petersen, Eugene T. (Box 23)
    - Peterson, Fred (Box 23)
    - Peterson, Kenneth L. (Box 23)
    - Petoskey, Merrill L. (Pete) (Box 23)
    - Petros, Spence (Box 23)
    - Phenicie, Jodene (Box 23)
    - Piavis, Mark C. (Box 23)
    - Pitoniak, Gregory E. (Box 23)
    - Pittman, Philip McM. (Box 23)
    - Plawecki, David A. (Box 23)
    - Points, David (Box 23)
    - Pollack, Lana (Box 23)
    - Ponte, Alfred (Box 23)
    - Poole, Daniel A. (Box 23)
    - Porreca, Vincent (Joe) (Box 23)
    - Porter, Paul (Box 23)
    - Posthumus, Dick (Box 23)
    - Postupalsky, Sergei (Box 23)
    - Poupore, Raymond (Box 23)
    - Powell, Roger Allen (Box 23)
    - Powell, Stanley M. (Box 23)
    - Power, Philip H. (Box 23)
    - Power, Thomas G. (Box 23)
    - Prawdzik, Thomas (Box 23)
    - Pregitzer, Theodore (Box 23)
    - Premo, George (Box 23)
    - Prescott, George A. (Box 23)
    - Price, Hubert, Jr. (Box 23)
    - Pridgeon, Dean (Box 23)
    - Pridnia, John D. (Box 23)
    - Profit, Kirk A. (Box 23)
    - Pruiett, William (Box 23)
    - Pruss, Stanley (Skip) (Box 23)
    - Purdy, Ralph W. (Box 23)
    - Pursell, Carl (Box 23)
    - Quick, Julane (Box 23)
    - Quinn, Ralph (Box 23)
    - Quinnett, Paul (Box 23)
    - Rademacher, Michael J. (Box 23)
    - Raimer, Howard (Box 23)
    - Ramsey, Buzz (Box 23)
    - Randall, Gary (Box 23)
    - Rasmussen, Roger (Box 23)
    - Razek, Lewis (Box 23)
    - Rector, Delbert (Box 23)
    - Redford, Robert (Box 23)
    - Reichel, Robert (Box 23)
    - Reid, William L. (Box 23)
    - Reinke, Carl (Box 23)
    - Reister, Russell W. (Box 23)
    - Reizen, Maurice S., M.D. (Box 23)
    - Renton, Sarah (Box 23)
    - Reynolds, Phyllis (Box 23)
    - Rhead, Kim A. (Box 23)
    - Richards, Don (Box 23)
    - Richey, David (Box 23)
    - Riggins, John (Box 23)
    - Ring, Robert R. (Box 23)
    - Risk, Paul (Box 23)
    - Rivers, Lynn (Box 23)
    - Robbins, Barbara (Box 23)
    - Robbins, D. Daniel (Box 23)
    - Robertson, David (Box 23)
    - Robertson, John M. (Box 23)
    - Robinson, William L. (Box 23)
    - Rocca, Sal (Box 23)
    - Rocca, Sue (Box 23)
    - Rockwell, Gordon (Box 23)
    - Rogers, Mike (Box 23)
    - Rollins-Page, Catherine (Box 23)
    - Rosenbaum, Paul (Box 23)
    - Roth, William K. (Box 23)
    - Rouman, James L. (Box 23)
    - Rowe, Kenneth (Box 23)
    - Rowe, Suzanne L. (Box 23)
    - Roy, Gordon (Box 23)
    - Ruckelshaus, William D. (Box 23)
    - Rue, Leonard Lee III (Box 23)
      (see also 8.5 x 11 envelopes)
    - Ruhl, Harry D. (Box 23)
    - Rustem, Raymond (Box 23)
    - Rustem, William (Box 23)
    - Rutherford, Jesse A. (Box 23)
    - Ryan, James R. (Box 23)
    - Ryan, William A. (Box 23)
    - Rydholm, C. Fred (Box 23)
    - Ryel, Lawrence A. (Box 23)
    - Ryynanen, Philip (Box 23)
    - Sackett, Wayne B. (Box 23)
    - Sagady, Alexander, Jr. (Box 23)
    - St. Pierre, Elizabeth Ann (Box 23)
    - Sams, Carl R. II (Box 23)
    - Sandborn, Mary (Box 23)
    - Sanderson, Dr. Joseph L. (Box 23)
    - Santo, Thomas L. (Box 23)
    - Saub, Joan (Box 23)
    - Saunders, Nelson W. (Box 23)
    - Sax, Joseph (Box 23)
    - Schafer, John (Box 23)
    - Schehr, Richard J. (Box 23)
    - Scherschligt, O.J. (Box 23)
    - Schingeck, Archie (Box 23)
    - Schmidt, Bill (Box 23)
    - Schmidt, Wayne (Box 23)
    - Schneider, Phillip W. (Box 23)
    - Scholle, August (Gus) (Box 23)
    - Schroer, Mary (Box 23)
    - Schrouder, John D. (Box 23)
    - Schuette, Bill (Box 23)
    - Schwarz, John J. H. (Box 23)
    - Schwarzkopf, H. Norman (Box 23)
    - Schwenke, Brett (Box 23)
    - Scieszka, Michael (Box 23)
    - Scott, John A. (Box 23)
    - Scott, Thomas E. (Box 23)
    - Seavey, Joseph (Box 23)
    - Sederburg, William A. (Box 23)
    - Segall, R. Thomas (Box 23)
    - Selby, John D. (Box 23)
    - Selfridge Ang Base (Box 23)
    - Sellers, Margaret (Box 23)
    - Serotkin, David M. (Box 23)
    - Shafer, Charles R. (Box 23)
    - Shafter, Charles R. (Box 23)
    - Shapton, Warren W. (Box 23)
    - Sharp, Eric (Box 23)
    - Sharpe, Thomas G. (Box 23)
    - Shearer, Ron (Box 23)
    - Shepard, James (Box 23)
    - Shepich, Stephen V. (Box 23)
    - Sheppard, Glen (Box 23)
    - Sheridan, Alfred A. (Box 23)
    - Sherk, John (Box 23)
    - Shick, Charles (Box 23)
    - Shinkle, Norman D. (Box 23)
    - Shugars, Dale (Box 23)
    - Sikarskie, James (Box 23)
    - Sikkema, Ken (Box 23)
    - Siljander, Mark D. (Box 23)
    - Simmon, Daniel A. (Box 23)
    - Sinkevics, John H. (Box 23)
    - Sitz, Rick (Box 23)
    - Skoog, Ronald O. (Box 23)
    - Skrel, Sylvia (Box 23)
    - Slaughter, Arthur E. (Box 23)
    - Sliger, Dr. Bernard F. (Box 23)
    - Slingerlend, Robert (Bud) (Box 23)
    - Smith, Dr. Alexander H. (Box 23)
    - Smith, Alma Wheeler (Box 23)
    - Smith, Bradley A. (Box 23)
    - Smith, Carlin (Box 23)
    - Smith, David (Box 23)
    - Smith, Douglas W. (Box 23)
    - Smith, Nick (Box 23)
    - Smith, Norman F. (Box 23)
    - Smith, Roy (Box 23)
    - Smith, Thomas M. (Box 23)
    - Smith, Virgil C. Jr. (Box 23)
    - Snell, Hilary F. (Box 23)
    - Snyder, Jay (Box 23)
    - Snyder, John (Box 23)
    - Snyder, Joseph M. (Box 23)
    - Soczek, Michael (Box 23)
    - Sodders, Betty (Box 23)
    - Sommerville, William (Box 23)
    - Spaniola, Francis R. (Box 23)
    - Spano, Josephine (Joey) M. (Box 23)
    - Sparks, Gordon R. (Box 23)
    - Spicer, Donald E. (Box 23)
    - Spillane, Mickey (Box 23)
    - Stabenow, Debbie (Box 23)
    - Stacy, Lad S. (Box 23)
    - Stallings, Henry III (Box 23)
    - Stallworth, Alma (Box 23)
    - Stanton, Barbara (Box 23)
    - Steffens, Ronald (Box 23)
    - Steil, Glenn D. (Box 23)
    - Stephens, Mark (Box 23)
    - Sterling, John K. (Box 23)
    - Stickler, Gerald (Box 23)
    - Stille, Leon (Box 23)
    - Stokes, Rodney A. (Box 23)
    - Stopczynski, Stanley (Box 23)
    - Stopczynski, Stephen (Box 23)
    - Stopczynski, Thaddeus C. (Box 23)
    - Stouffer, Marty (Box 23)
    - Stout, Gene (Box 23)
    - Strait, Joseph Jr. (Box 23)
    - Strand, John (Box 23)
    - Stroh, Peter (Box 23)
    - Sullivan, Clark (Box 23)
    - Sullivan, Richard (Box 23)
    - Summerall, Pat (Box 23)
    - Sweet, Brenda (Box 23)
    - Sygo, James J. (Box 23)
    - Symons, Joyce (Box 23)
    - Tabor, State Rep. Susan (Box 23)
    - Tait, William L. (Box 23)
    - Tanner, Helen (Box 23)
    - Tanner, Dr. Howard A. (Box 23)
    - Tatter, Jordan (Box 23)
    - Taylor, Sylvia (Box 23)
    - Taylor, Zack (Box 23)
    - Terrell, Ethel (Box 23)
    - Tesanovich, Paul (Box 23)
    - Textor, Ted (Box 23)
    - Thiel, Jan (Box 23)
    - Thomas, Gene (Box 23)
    - Tierney, Dennis P. (Box 23)
    - Timm, Richard (Box 23)
    - Tipper, Lewis (Box 23)